Guide to the American Theological Library Association Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Administrative Records, Series II
  - President of Board of Directors Records
    - Roscoe Pierson (1966-1967)
      - Correspondence: Committee on Reprinting, 1961-1965 (Box 10, Folder 130)
      - Correspondence: Authors and Publishers, Committee on Reprinting, 1961-1962 (Box 10, Folder 131)
      - Correspondence: Committee on Reprinting, 1961-1971 (Box 10, Folder 132-133)
      - Correspondence: Conference, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 134)
      - Correspondence: Louisville Conference, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 135)
      - Library Development Program, 1962-1967 (Box 10, Folder 136)
      - Correspondence, 1957-1962 (Box 10, Folder 137)
    - Arthur Jones (1967-1968)
      - Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 138)
    - Maria Grossman (1968-1969)
      - Correspondence and Reports, 1967-1970 (Box 11, Folder 139-140)
    - Harold Prince (1968-1970)
      - Correspondence, Reports and Minutes, 1968-1970 (Box 11, Folder 141-143)
    - Henry Scherer (1970-1971)
      - Correspondence, Reports and Minutes, 1968-1971 (Box 11, Folder 144)
    - Genevieve Kelly (1971-1972)
      - Minutes, Reports, Proposals and Miscellaneous, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 145)
      - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 146)
    - Peter VandenBerge (1972-1973)
      - Correspondence and Notes: Incorporation and Conference, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 147)
      - Correspondence and Agenda: Executive Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 148)
      - Correspondence: A-Z, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 149)
      - Correspondence: A-L, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 150)
      - Correspondence: M-V, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 151)
      - Correspondence: W-Z, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 152)
      - ATLA Ability and Interest Questionnaire: Responses A-K, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 153)
      - ATLA Ability and Interest Questionnaire: Responses L-Z, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 154)
    - John Baker-Batsel (1973-1974)
      - Proposal: Cooperative Acquisition and Cataloging Project, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 155)
      - Correspondence and Minutes: Executive Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 12, Folder 156)
      - Correspondence: Conference, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 157)
      - Correspondence, Minutes and Reports: Council on the Study of Religion, 1972-1974 (Box 12, Folder 158)
      - Correspondence and Miscellaneous Items, 1972-1976 (Box 12, Folder 159)
      - Correspondence and Reports: Dismissal of Librarians at the University of Chicago, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 160)
      - Copyright Action, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 161)
      - Conferences, 1973-1975 (Box 13, Folder 162)
      - Correspondence and Notes: ATLA and ATS Task Force, 1973-1976 (Box 13, Folder 163)
      - Board of Directors Midwinter Meeting, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 164)
      - Correspondence: Foundations and Funding, 1974-1977 (Box 13, Folder 165)
      - Correspondence: Ad Hoc Committee on Serials Control, 1976-1979 (Box 13, Folder 166)
    - Oscar Burdick (1974-1975)
      - Systems and Standards, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 167)
      - Bureau of Personnel and Placement, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 168)
      - Minutes and Drafts: Board of Directors, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 169)
      - Correspondence: Board of Directors, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 170)
    - Roland Kircher (1975-1976)
      - Correspondence and Reports: Conference, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 171)
    - Erich Schultz (1976-1977)
      - Special Libraries Association: Salary Survey, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 172)
      - Correspondence: Aids to a Theological Library, 1974-1976 (Box 13, Folder 173)
      - Correspondence, 1974-1977 (Box 13, Folder 174-175)
      - Executive Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 176)
      - Correspondence, Reports and Handbook: Conferences, 1975-1977 (Box 14, Folder 177)
      - Correspondence and Reports: Periodical Exchange Committee, 1975-1977 (Box 14, Folder 178)
      - Correspondence and Reports: Council of National Library Associations, 1975-1977 (Box 14, Folder 179)
      - Correspondence: Universal Serials and Book Exchange, 1975-1977 (Box 14, Folder 180)
      - Correspondence and Reports: Library Consultation Program, 1975-1977 (Box 14, Folder 181)
      - Correspondence and Reports: Membership Committee, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 182)
      - Designs: ATLA Logo and Seal, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 183)
      - Correspondence, 1972-1981 (Box 14, Folder 184)
      - Correspondence and Notes, 1984-1985 (Box 14, Folder 185)
    - John Trotti (1977-1978)
      - Correspondence and Minutes: Executive Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 186)
      - Correspondence and Reports: Forming Regional Chapters, 1972-1976 (Box 14, Folder 187)
      - ATLA Needs and Contracts with Foundations, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 188)
      - Correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 14, Folder 189)
      - Committee on Serials Control, 1977-1978 (Box 14, Folder 190)
      - Correspondence and Reports: Midwinter Meeting, 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 191)
      - Correspondence: 31st Annual Conference, 1976-1977 (Box 15, Folder 192)
    - Elmer O'Brien (1978-1979)
      - Correspondence: 32nd Annual Conference, 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 193)
      - Correspondence, Programs and Contracts: 32nd Annual Conference, 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 194)
      - Correspondence and Biographical Material: 32nd Annual Conference, 1977-1978 (Box 15, Folder 195)
      - Committee on Standards of Accreditation, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 196)
      - Report: Committee on Membership, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 197)
      - Council on the Study of Religion, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 198)
      - Correspondence and Draft Proposals: Committee for Preservation of Theological Materials, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 199)
      - Correspondence and Grant Proposal: Periodical Indexing, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 200)
      - Correspondence and Agenda: Board of Directors, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 201)
      - Correspondence and Reports: Committee on Collection, Evaluation and Development, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 202)
      - Correspondence and Reports: Committee on Continuing Education and Professional Development, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 203)
      - Correspondence: Conference, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 204)
      - Consultation Program, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 205)
      - Correspondence, Minutes and Reports: Committee on Publication, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 206)
      - Correspondence and Reports: Committee on Reader Services, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 207)
      - Correspondence and Reports: Foundations, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 208)
      - Correspondence and Minutes: Finance, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 209)
      - Correspondence and Memoranda: Scholar Press, 1978-1980 (Box 15, Folder 210)
      - Correspondence and Reports: Board of Microtext, 1978-1980 (Box 16, Folder 211)
      - Correspondence, Reports and Minutes: Committee on Serials Control, 1978-1980 (Box 16, Folder 212)
      - Correspondence: Committee on Cataloging and Classification, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 213)
      - Correspondence and Agenda: 33rd Annual Conference, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 214)
    - Simeon Daly (1979-1981)
      - Reports, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 215)
      - Library Building Project, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 216)
      - Task Force 80, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 217)
      - Notes, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 218)
      - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 219)
      - Correspondence and Reports, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 220)
      - Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 221-227)
      - Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 17, Folder 228-238)
      - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 239)
      - Correspondence and Reports, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 240)
      - Correspondence, Reports and Notes, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 240a)
      - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 126, Folder 13)
    - Jerry Campbell (1981-1982)
      - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 241)
      - Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 126, Folder 14-20)
    - Robert Dvorak (1982-1983)
      - Notes (Box 18, Folder 242)
      - Correspondence, 1981-1983 (Box 18, Folder 243-245)
      - Letter from Donn Michael Ferris, 1983 (Box 128, Folder 5)
    - Martha Aycock (1983-1984)
      - Correspondence: Bibliographic Systems, 1982-1984 (Box 18, Folder 246)
      - Correspondence: Collection Development, 1982-1984 (Box 18, Folder 247)
      - Notes and Correspondence: Conference, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 248)
      - Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 249-250)
      - Correspondence and Reports: Project 2000, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 251)
      - Correspondence and Reports, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 252)
      - Notes and Correspondence: Board Meeting, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 253)
      - Correspondence: Board, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 254)
      - Correspondence: Program Committee, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 255)
      - Correspondence: Reader's Service, 1981-1984 (Box 19, Folder 256)
      - Correspondence: Board of Directors, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 257)
      - Correspondence: Committees, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 258)
      - Notes and Correspondence: Committees, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 259)
    - Sara Myers (1985-1986)
      - Correspondence, 1985-1990 (Box 19, Folder 260)
      - Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Stephen Peterson (1986-1987)
      - Report: Project 2000, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 261)
      - Correspondence: Project 2000, 1981-1988 (Box 19, Folder 262)
      - Correspondence, 1983-1988 (Box 19, Folder 263-267)
      - Project 2000 files: correspondence, questionnaires, survey results, reports, 1980-1987 (Box 127, Folder 5-29)
    - Rosalyn Lewis
      - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 128, Folder 10)
    - Eugene McLeod
      - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 126, Folder 41)
  - Vice President Records
    - G. Paul Hamm (1978-1980)
      - Correspondence and Reports, 1978-1979 (Box 20, Folder 268)
    - Martha Aycock (1982-1983)
      - Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 269)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Correspondence
      - General, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 270)
      - Edinburgh Trip, 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 271)
    - Materials added 2006
      - Pay schedule and employee benefits, 1985 (Box 122, Folder 6)
      - Information about employee benefits and personnel policies, 1986 (Box 122, Folder 7)
      - Employees handbook and personnel policies, ca.1986 (Box 122, Folder 8)
      - Job descriptions, 1988 Feb (Box 122, Folder 9)
- Committees, Series III
  - Annual Conference Committee
    Scope and Contents
    See also Program Committee
    - Correspondence, 1978-1982 (Box 21, Folder 272)
    - Correspondence, Reports and Budgets, 1976-1981 (Box 21, Folder 273)
    - Notes and Reports, 1979-1982 (Box 21, Folder 274)
    - Conference Material (Box 21, Folder 275)
    - Handbook, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 276)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1986 (Box 21, Folder 277-277a)
  - Appraisal Committee
    - Correspondence and Reports, 1968-1970 (Box 21, Folder 278)
  - ATLA Needs (Ad Hoc)
    - Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 31, Folder 399)
    - Correspondence, 1969-1977 (Box 32, Folder 400-401)
    - Correspondence and Reports, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 402)
    - Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 32, Folder 403)
  - Brochure Committee
    - Correspondence (Box 21, Folder 279)
  - Building and Equipment Committee
    - Correspondence, 1957-1968 (Box 21, Folder 280)
  - By-Laws Revision
    - Correspondence and Drafts, 1982-1985 (Box 38, Folder 470)
  - Cataloging and Classification Committee
    - Cataloging Report Forms (Box 22, Folder 281)
    - Correspondence: Cooperative Cataloging, 1963-1972 (Box 22, Folder 282)
    - Correspondence, 1949-1979 (Box 22, Folder 283-284)
    - Correspondence: Ecumenical Index, 1965 (Box 22, Folder 285)
    - Correspondence: Publishers, 1971-1972 (Box 22, Folder 286)
    - Correspondence: LC Subject Headings, 1965-1973 (Box 22, Folder 287)
    - Correspondence: National Union Catalog and New Serials Titles, 1960-1972 (Box 22, Folder 288)
    - Newsletter, 1972-1977 (Box 22, Folder 289)
    - Correspondence: Newsletter, 1972-1977 (Box 22, Folder 290)
    - Correspondence: Reclassification, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 291)
    - Correspondence: Representation on ALA Catalog Code Revision Committee, 1961-1977 (Box 22, Folder 292)
    - Correspondence: Study on Theological Subject Headings, 1960-1967;1972-1974 (Box 22, Folder 293)
    - Proposal and Correspondence: Library Automation, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 294)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1977 (Box 23, Folder 295)
    - Genre Terms, 1983 (Box 23, Folder 296)
    - Catalog: Presbyterian and Reformed Renewal Ministries International, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 297)
    - Reports and Surveys, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 298)
  - Collection Evaluation and Development Section / Committee
    - Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987, 1989 (Box 137, Folder 7)
    - Reports and background material, 1984-1986 (Box 137, Folder 8)
    - Copies of Collection Development Policies of theological libraries, 1985-1986 (Box 137, Folder 9)
  - Executive Committee
    - Meeting Reports, 1954-1957 (Box 23, Folder 299)
    - Correspondence, 1954-1956 (Box 23, Folder 300-301)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1955-1969; 1961; 1963-1971 (Box 23, Folder 302)
    - Correspondence, 1958-1974 (Box 23, Folder 303-304)
    - Correspondence: Project 2000, 1981-1984 (Box 23, Folder 305)
    - Reports, 1982-1982; 1988 (Box 24, Folder 306)
    - Meeting Reports, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 307)
  - Executive Secretary Search
    - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 472)
  - Exhibit Study Committee
    - Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 24, Folder 309)
  - Faculty Status Committee
    - Correspondence, Reports, Questionnaire, 1960-1978 (Box 24, Folder 310)
    - Reports and Correspondence, 1973-1978 (Box 38, Folder 473)
  - Financial Affairs (Ad Hoc)
    - Notes, Reports and Correspondence, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 404)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 32, Folder 405-406)
    - Reports, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 407)
  - Financial Assistance from Foundations Committee
    - Correspondence and Reports, 1957-1958 (Box 24, Folder 311)
    - Minutes, Proposals and Correspondence, 1965-1967 (Box 24, Folder 312)
  - Financial Management Committee
    - Correspondence and reports, 1984-1985 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1986-1988 (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1988-1990 (Box 126, Folder 26-27)
  - Fiscal Management
    - Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 38, Folder 467)
  - General Standing
    - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 475)
  - Historical Documentation / Historical Records Committee
    - Reports and Correspondence, 1973-1993 (Box 38, Folder 468)
    - Correspondence, 1951-1985 (Box 38, Folder 469)
    - Reports and Correspondence, including from Fr. Simeon Daly, 1991-1994 (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - Joint Committee on Library Resources
    - Report (Box 38, Folder 471)
  - Legal Responsibilities
    - Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 38, Folder 466)
  - Library Development Committee
    - Bulletin and Reports, 1961-1966 (Box 24, Folder 313)
    - Reports, 1964 (Box 24, Folder 314)
    - Correspondence and Reports, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 315)
    - Correspondence, 1942-1960 (Box 24, Folder 316)
  - Library Standards Committee
    - Correspondence: AATS and ATLA, 1951-1952 (Box 24, Folder 317)
    - Reports: AATS and ATLA, 1951-1952 (Box 24, Folder 318)
    - Reports and Correspondence (Box 24, Folder 319)
  - Long Range Planning Committee
    - Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 38, Folder 462-463)
  - Master List of Research Studies in Religion
    - Correspondence and Reports, 1948-1951; 1966-1968; 1971 (Box 25, Folder 320)
  - Membership Committee
    - Reports and Correspondence, 1956-1980 (Box 25, Folder 321-322)
    - Questionnaire (Box 25, Folder 323)
    - Reports, 1982-1983 (Box 25, Folder 324)
    - Advertising, 1980-1981 (Box 25, Folder 325)
    - Correspondence and Reports: Prospective Members, 1980-1981 (Box 25, Folder 326)
    - Correspondence: New Members, 1981-1982 (Box 25, Folder 327)
    - List of Members (Box 25, Folder 328)
    - Correspondence, 1978-1997 (Box 25, Folder 329-331)
  - Newsletter Committee
    - Reports, 1953-1964 (Box 25, Folder 332)
    - Requests, 1976-1977 (Box 25, Folder 333)
    - Mailing List (Box 25, Folder 334)
    - Correspondence and Reports, 1974-1976 (Box 25, Folder 335)
    - Reports (Box 25, Folder 336)
  - Nominating Committee
    - Correspondence, 1958-1976 (Box 26, Folder 337)
    - Ballots, 1961-1977 (Box 26, Folder 338)
    - Correspondence and Reports, 1973-1986 (Box 26, Folder 339-344)
    - Correspondence and Reports, 1985-1992 (Box 127, Folder 1-3)
  - Personnel and Placement Committee
    - Correspondence, 1959-1973 (Box 26, Folder 345)
    - Directory (Box 26, Folder 346)
    - Positions Open, 1966-1981 (Box 27, Folder 347-348)
  - Personnel Exchange (Ad Hoc)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1977 (Box 32, Folder 408-409)
    - Applications, 1976-1978 (Box 32, Folder 410)
  - Preservation of Theological Materials (Ad Hoc)
    - Reports, 1978-1981 (Box 38, Folder 464)
    - Correspondence, 1978-1983 (Box 38, Folder 465)
  - Program Committee
    - Correspondence and reports, 1981-1982 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1982-1983 (Box 35, Folder 432)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1983 (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1984 (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence and reports, 1988-1991 (Box 138, Folder 7)
  - Publication Committee
    - Brochures (Box 27, Folder 349)
    - Bibliography Series Publication Files (Box 27, Folder 350)
    - Bibliography Series Rejections, 1972-1978 (Box 27, Folder 351)
    - Index to Festschriften in Religion (Box 27, Folder 352)
    - Monograph Series Brochures (Box 27, Folder 353)
    - Correspondence: Monograph Series, 1970-1981 (Box 27, Folder 354-355)
    - Monograph Series: Publication Files (Box 28, Folder 356-358)
    - Monograph Series: Publication Policy (Box 28, Folder 359)
    - Monograph Series: Recommended Titles, 1968-1976 (Box 28, Folder 360)
    - Monograph Series: Rejections, 1971-1978 (Box 28, Folder 361)
    - Publisher's Decisions on Religious Books, 1948 (Box 28, Folder 362)
    - Correspondence: Subcommittee on Union List of Serials, 1974-1981 (Box 28, Folder 363)
    - Progress Reports: Subcommittee on Union List of Serials (Box 28, Folder 364)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1985-1988 (Box 29, Folder 365)
    - Editor's Meeting, 1980-1983 (Box 29, Folder 366-367)
    - Expenses, 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 368)
    - Correspondence: Scholar's Press, 1979-1980 (Box 29, Folder 369)
    - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 370)
  - Reader's Service Committee
    - Correspondence and Reports, 1972-1979 (Box 29, Folder 371)
    - Reports (Box 29, Folder 372)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1986 (Box 29, Folder 373-374)
  - Recruitment and Education for Theological Librarianship Committee
    - Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box 29, Folder 375)
    - Questionnaire and Results, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 376)
    - Reports, 1957-1958 (Box 29, Folder 377)
  - Relationships with Learned Societies
    - Reports, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 460)
  - Reprinting Committee
    - Correspondence, 1961-1964 (Box 30, Folder 378)
  - Scholarship Committee
    - Correspondence: Lilly Endowment, 1959-1964 (Box 30, Folder 379)
    - Application: Lilly Endowment (Box 30, Folder 380)
    - Reports: Lilly Endowment (Box 30, Folder 381)
    - Requests: Lilly Endowment (Box 30, Folder 382)
    - Correspondence and Reports: Sealantic Fund (Box 30, Folder 383)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 30, Folder 384)
  - Serials Control Committee
    - Proposals to Foundations, 1979-1980 (Box 33, Folder 412)
    - Grant Application, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 413)
    - Expenses (Box 33, Folder 414)
    - Reports (Box 33, Folder 415-418)
    - Questionnaire (Box 33, Folder 419)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1980 (Box 34, Folder 420-428)
    - Correspondence and Applications for Grants, 1974-1978 (Box 35, Folder 429)
    - Correspondence: Proposals to Foundations, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 430)
    - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 431)
  - Standards of Accreditation Committee
    - Correspondence, 1957-1981 (Box 30, Folder 385)
    - Guidelines (Box 30, Folder 386)
    - Reports (Box 30, Folder 387)
    - Questionnaire: Theological Librarian Job Description (Box 30, Folder 388)
    - Reports and Correspondence, 1969-1979 (Box 31, Folder 389)
    - Handbook, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 390)
  - Standards for Non-Print Media
    - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 411)
  - Statistics Committee
    - Correspondence, 1961-1974 (Box 31, Folder 391)
    - Chart: Results of Questionnaire, 1951 (Box 31, Folder 392)
    - Questionnaire: Forms and Results (Box 31, Folder 393)
    - Reports, 1967-1995 (Box 31, Folder 394)
    - Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 31, Folder 395)
  - Strategic Planning Committee
    - Reports, 1988-1990 (Box 37, Folder 456-457)
    - Sourcebook, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 458)
    - Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 37, Folder 459)
    - Material added 2006, 1990 (Box 126, Folder 39-40)
  - Sub-Committee on Appointments
    - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 474)
  - Systems and Standards Committee
    - Correspondence, 1953-1975 (Box 31, Folder 396)
  - Task Force on Preservation of Religious Monographs
    - Reports and Correspondence, 1981-1983 (Box 37, Folder 461)
    - Materials added 2006, 1983-1984 (Box 126, Folder 43)
  - Tellers Committee
    - Correspondence and Ballot Information (Box 35, Folder 433)
    - Reports: Peoplenet, 1985-1988 (Box 35, Folder 434-436)
    - Correspondence and Drafts: Peoplenet, 1984-1987 (Box 35, Folder 437)
    - Reports (Box 35, Folder 438)
    - Reports: Denominations (Box 36, Folder 439)
    - Directory and Profile (Box 36, Folder 440)
    - Reports and Correspondence, 1983-1990 (Box 36, Folder 441-445)
    - Membership List, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 446)
    - Correspondence, 1979-1984 (Box 36, Folder 447-451)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 37, Folder 452-453)
    - Correspondence: Newsletter, 1988-1990 (Box 37, Folder 454)
    - Correspondence, 1988-1990 (Box 37, Folder 455)
  - Theological Library Extension Services
    - Correspondence, 1948-1950 (Box 31, Folder 397-398)
  - Materials added 2006
    - AATS/ATLA Task Force on Theological Libraries in the 1970s, 1973 (Box 122, Folder 11)
    - AATS/ATLA Task Force on Theological Libraries in the 1970s, 1972-1973 (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Needs - correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 122, Folder 12)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Needs - questionnaire and report, 1976-1977 (Box 122, Folder 13-14)
    - Ad Hoc Committeee on Financial Management, 1985-1986 (Box 122, Folder 15-16)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on Storage and Preservation, 1979-1984 (Box 122, Folder 17)
    - Ad Hoc Committee on the Implementation of the AATS/ATLA Task Force Report, 1973-1976 (Box 122, Folder 18)
    - Change of Bibliographic Systems Committee to the Technical Services Division, 1990 (Box 122, Folder 19)
    - Future Site Committee, 1987 (Box 122, Folder 20)
    - Publications Committee, 1987-1991 (Box 122, Folder 21-22)
    - Task Force '80, 1980 (Box 122, Folder 23)
    - Task Force to Study the Feasibility of an ATLA Journal, 1974 (Box 122, Folder 24)
    - Theological Users Group (TUG), 1985-1990 (Box 122, Folder 25-30)
    - Joint Executive Committee of Boards of Index and Preservation, 1988-1990 (Box 126, Folder 31-38)
- Board of Index, Series IV
  - Meetings
    - Minutes, 1957-1973 Jun (Box 39, Folder 476-484)
    - Minutes, 1973 Nov-1977 (Box 40, Folder 485-494)
    - Minutes, 1978-1980 (Box 41, Folder 495-502)
    - Minutes, 1980-1982 (Box 42, Folder 503-512)
    - Minutes, 1983-1986 (Box 43, Folder 513-518)
    - Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 44, Folder 519-520)
  - Reports
    - Periodical Move, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 521)
    - Editor's Report, 1978 (Box 44, Folder 522)
    - RIO-RIT, 1980-1981 (Box 44, Folder 523-523a)